stockmusicsite.com 2011-11-02

# StockMusicSite.com Privacy Policy

wav sound bites,  
audio wav files,  
downloadable wav sound effects,  
sound effects movies,  
d eagle shot wav,  
dj name sound,  
suspense sound effects wav,  
does movie maker have sound effects,  
free animal sound clips,  
owl sounds for download,  
money sound effect,  
dog noises,  
sound effects bank,  
intro sound effects free,  
sound effects dog wood,  
explosion sound effect,  
listen to free wind chime sounds,  
sound effects theatre,  
mp3s download,  
sound design 

|   
---  
  
**Privacy Policy of StockMusicSite.com  
**   

We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.**

** 1.  What Personal Information Do We Collect and Save?**

  * **Information You Provide.**  We receive and store information you enter.  For example, when you search for or buy a product, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card.  You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features.  We collect and save the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you.  In addition, if you choose, we may share your information with other companies who provide goods or services that you are interested in.  Please see the ?opt-in/opt-out? selection in Section 4 of this policy.   
 
  * **Cookies.** Like many websites, we use "cookies".  Your browser will automatically store one cookie that allows us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience.  And most importantly, the cookie is what maintains your "logged in" state once you register and login to the site.  If you delete our cookie from your browser, you will no longer be logged into our web site.

**Other Information:** Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address.  IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted.  In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site. 

** 2.  How Do We Use Your Information?**

  * **Customized Shopping.   **We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized shopping experience.   
 
  * **Composers and Publishers.   **When you purchase audio content at StockMusicSite.com, your contact information will be shared with the composer(s) and publisher(s) of each track to inform them about how their music is being used and who is using it.  
 
  * **Agents.** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.   
 
  * **Special Offers**.  We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to ?opt-out? of receiving such offers.  In addition, we may also send you special offers from other companies.  Again, you may ?opt-out?.  If we send you offers from other businesses, we do not share your personal information with them.  The offers come directly through us.  Please see the ?opt-in/opt-out? selection at the end of this policy.    
 
  * **Business Transfers**. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, sites or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that we are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.  
 
  * **Law Enforcement.    **If we receive a lawful court order to release account or other personal information then we will comply with the law.  We will also release information when necessary to protect the life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.   
 
  * **Internal Reference.**   The information we collect and save is used for internal reference purposes, to administer our business operations in a proper manner.

** 3.  How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?**

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 
  * We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list. 
  * We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion. 
  * We limit access to your information on a ?need to know? basis. 
  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 
  * No system can guarantee absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical security.  However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure. 

**4.   Your Choice:  Opt-in or Opt-out.**

> It is your choice whether to receive emails or special offers from us about sales promotions and new music libraries that are added to our site.  
>  By default, newly registered clients are opted-in.  During registration, to not receive the emails, please opt-out.

** 5.  Children**

>  We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

** 6.  Other Websites**

> Various Web sites may be linked to from this site.  If you click through to another web site, your privacy depends on the policy of that site.  We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy.  Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others.  You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance ([www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/)).

** 7.  Contact Us**

> If you ever need assistance with the features, products or services offered on this web site, please contact us at [ info@stockmusicsite.com](mailto:info@stockmusicsite.com) and we will be happy to assist you. 

** 8.  Reserved Rights**

> We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future.

*************************************  

aiff sounds,  
download a lot of sound effects,  
audiowarez,  
planet exploding sound effect,  
splash sound effect,  
swoosh sound effects to download,  
free fx house on fire sound files,  
sounds of a ticking clock to download,  
free window live messenger sounds,  
family feud game show sound effects,  
free mobile sound effects,  
cat sound effects,  
rocket sound effect free,  
bagpipe music sound files,  
sound effects wind blowing,  
wookey sound effects,  
free chicken wav sound effects,  
sound effects wav files,  
get sound effects,  
game sound effects
